I have to do this application by Director of North Campus Industries and Scott Truster's friend, Mr. Steve, what's up?
I'm just talking to him on the phone.
I saw you pull it up.
He's so excited about it.
I would just thank you for this day.
I would just thank you for another day of life.
It's never promised to us.
Thank you for helping us.
Thank you for our community.
We pray for our souls and counsel.
And if you're pretty off with his staff,
I would just say, I would say, lead this city.
I would just thank you for anyway.
I'd like to support other students throughout there representing our school.
Fifty different countries will want to bless them.
All of this help us as we all work together.
She's just name a pretty believe in the good things.
We'll buy more more.
Thank you.
Please join in the pledge.
I'd like to lead you just to the flag of the United States of America.
And to read about that before, to the States, one nation.
I have died.
And this will deliver to you just as far up.
Okay.
Item four is public input unscheduled personal parents.
Anyone the audience wishes to address the authority on any agenda items.
Item five is considered agenda staff is recommending item six and seven,
which are claims and minutes for the consent agenda.
If there are no questions on any of those items,
an entertaining motion to approve the consent agenda as recommended.
So moved.
And second roll call please.
Louis I.
Western or get results.
Item eight is the business and the business anyone.
Item nine staff report.
So you're packet.
The staff available for questions if they're in.
Item ten is trust security announcements.
Item eleven is adjourned.
We have both to adjourn the issue a meeting.
So should you adjourn.
Second.
roll call please.
Western.